## Alexandra Campbell

1+ (602) 625-2503

email AlexandraBrinnCampbell@gmail.com

GitHub killeraliens

LinkedIn /alexandra-brinn-campbell

www alexandrabrinn.com

Dedicated programmer coming from a background in industrial design and graphics. I love scripting digital experiences for people and can offer a range of both creative and technical skills. Always ready to work with any new tools for the iob.

#### Dev

Postgres • Express • React • Node.js • Ruby on Rails • HTML5 • CSS/SCSS • Bootstrap • jQuery • SQL • MVC architecture • REST API • OOP • git & GitHub • Heroku • now & Zeit • server-side testing in Mocha, Chai, Supertest • frontend testing with Jest, Enzyme

### UX & UI

CSS Grid & Flexbox • responsive design • Adobe Creative Suite • Webflow • Invision • Sketch • Figma • Whimsical • Mindnode • AutoCad • user interviews & testing • branding & creative content

## **Projects**

#### Goat's Guide (pivot design) | goatsguide.com

If you know about an upcoming concert, fest, or tour, share the flier on Goat's Guide - a DIY bulletin board for poster artwork and event information. This is a new strategy on a passion project utilizing the PERN stack along with TDD and CI techniques. Custom authorization and protected endpoints make both the frontend and REST API private to the community. Read more about the project and get demo account access here.

PostgreSQL • Express • React • Node.js • CSS • REST API • SQL • Zeit/Now • Heroku • TDD server-side • Mocha, Chai, and Supertest

## Goat's Guide MVP | goats-guide.herokuapp.com

Goat's Guide is a heavy metal event & venue database concept as well as an ongoing study in UX design. I am currently reworking this project using React, Express, and Node.js to reduce app loading time, and improve user experience while encouraging more complete and user-sourced event data. Check out the early Invision prototype here.

Ruby on Rails • HTML-scraping • Watir • Nokogiri • Sidekiq background tasks • Devise gem auth • PostgreSQL • Heroku

You can find more projects on my website at alexandrabrinn.com

# **Experience**

Apr 2015 - Jul 2018

Burgeon Group | Design Project Manager | instagram @BurgeonGroup

- Managed projects through a complete lifecycle by coordinating with stakeholders, including clients, designers, and fabrication departments.
- Supported spatial design, client communications and presentations, marketing content, and file management.
- Executed and presented technical drafting, construction & installation plan documents weekly.

2012 - 2015

Demi Coffee, Phoenix AZ | Owner/Operations | instagram @DemiCoffee

- Known in the community for a unique (tiny!) space, fantastic cold brew, and attention to quality.
- Provided exceptional customer service and a niche experience with creative food, beverages, and atmosphere.

2012 - Current

Curiotile | Design and Development

- A personal project which showcases knowledge on process, materials, and design.
- Iterative "flatpack" designs in stainless and powder coat steel, custom displays & storage solutions.
- · Images & descriptions available on request.

2009 - 2013

Ah Diós | Freelance Graphics & Branding

- Collaborated with a small team in the areas of web, film, branding, and UX design.
- Supported brand development through signage, web, and packaging graphics for Visual+Intent, Cartel Coffee Lab, Request Manufacturing, and Sooh Media.

### Education

May 2019 - Feb 2020

Thinkful. JavaScript, Node Fullstack Engineering Program

Jan - Mar 2019

Le Wagon, London. Ruby on Rails Coding Bootcamp

Feb - Mar 2018

General Assembly 8 week course in UX design

**BDES Industrial Design, 2007** 

Emily Carr University, Vancouver BC